Go hero one more time!
Ben 10: Alien Swarm is a action, tv movie, science
fiction film directed by Alex Winter.
Ben and a mysterious girl from his past must prevent an
alien threat from destroying the world.
Ben Tennyson, played by Ryan Kelley.
Gwen Tennyson, played by Galadriel Stineman.
Kevin E. Levin, played by Nathan Keyes.
Elena Validus, played by Alyssa Diaz.
Victor Validus, played by Herbert Siguenza.
Grandpa Max Tennyson, played by Barry Corbin.
Ben 10: Alien Swarm is a 2009 American superhero film directed by
Alex Winter and written by John Turman and James Krieg.
Based on the Cartoon Network animated series Ben 10: Alien Force (2008–2010) and the second live-action film in the Ben 10 franchise following Ben
10: Race Against Time (2007), it stars Ryan Kelley, Galadriel Stineman, Nathan Keyes, Alyssa Diaz, Herbert Siguenza, and Barry Corbin.
The film takes place during the events of Alien Force, later receiving follow-up
episodes in the sequel series Ben 10: Ultimate Alien (2010–2012).
Ben 10: Alien Swarm held its world premiere in London on November 15, 2009, and premiered on
Cartoon Network on November 25, 2009, where it was watched by 4.02 million viewers.
The film explores themes of extraterrestrial technology,
transformation, alien, based on cartoon, alien race.
The tone is thought_provoking.